So.
Hello, hi, we are Team Qnovate.
So we are building a specific project
assistant agent that is an industry agent
for manufacturers who sell for
construction projects. Now,
there was a strategic problem where an
appliance maker selling into hotels,
apartments.
senior livings, student housing wins.
I mean,
they win deals over a year before that
specific building opens, right?
Lead arrive, lead can arrive by, you know,
emails, phone, you know,
weekly external spreadsheets,
maybe some integrations. And, you know,
each one of these is retyped into the CRM.
And I mean,
if users are checking for duplicates,
if you are matching for four different
companies, you know, if it is judged by,
you know, gut feelings, I mean,
this would take approx 5 hours of an
sales rep, you know,
with duplicates and missing stakeholders
and all records of.
Why, like?
So what we have built is a specific agent.
Now what that specific agent will do is
it will do this specific stuff and try to
stuff and then try to minimise the
efforts of a sales rep or maybe minimise
to reduce the hours of a sales rep who's
working on it.
to, let's say,
maybe 10 to 15 minutes from 5 hours for
one specific project, right? So again,
this would give a user or this would give
the sales rep a more flexibility on a few
things that he can work on if he was not
working on previously, right?
So let's take the first scenario.
Where we got an e-mail from,
we got an e-mail from Eli Mishra,
and then this is something that I got an
e-mail where it is talking about, hey,
can it is giving me some details about
the project that is there.
This is related to a specific residence
which is...
Linwood Hotel and Residences and then we
got a lead, right?
We got basically a lead. I got a lead.
Now what I will do is I'll simply copy
this and then I'll paste this.
I will paste that specific e-mail into
this and I've just given a specific
prompt where you can capture the details
from it.
Now what my AI agent will do is it will
run and at the back end it will create
certain project intakes.
So the first thing it will create is
first it will create.
it will cheque and it will ask for,
you know,
whether I need to create this specific
project or not. Then what it will do,
then it will ask me for, you know,
whether I can run a verdict or not. Now,
what is a verdict? So basically,
verdict is, you know,
verdict is based on certain scoring
mechanisms that we already have.
So for example,
Now,
these verdicts take place by keeping in
factors like what should be the scoring
factors, what should be the scoring rules,
what should be the priority risk,
you know,
what should be the priority brands or
bands of this specific project intake,
what should be the whole process behind
this, right? It should do.
it should do all that.
And then this is everything that is
configurable by an admin or by a user.
So this is a user specific or maybe let's
call it a business specific thing, right?
So the agent will automatically analyse
this data and then it will give us a
verdict on that. Now,
since this is a taking,
this was not taking some time.
So as you can see,
Now,
the agent has given me certain details.
The agent has given me all those details,
and now it is asking me whether I can
create a project or not.
So I can simply say, yes,
you can create it.
So what I have given is I have simply say,
yes, can you add this category? That's it.
And then now I've.
pasted my specific prompt that was there.
So I have simply said, yes,
add this project category,
this is a new build,
the specification should be open,
and then create it. Now at the back end,
this will create a project intake.
It will not create a project,
it will not create a project,
it will create a project intake.
It will create a project intake.
Now what is a project intake?
A project intake is basically before a
project creation,
it will create one more entity that will
do its job. Now if you can see,
so let's wait where it is creating that
and then let's try to refresh it.
Once the project intake is created,
then we will obviously run a project.
verdict on it.
And then the AI will basically run that
specific wording,
keeping in mind the scoring factors that
we have, the priority bands we have,
whether it is able to search for a
duplicate or not. Now,
what this agent is actually doing is it
is also at the back end,
it is also searching, you know,
these type of opportunities.
There is an opportunity linked with this
type of projects. There is a...
There is some more details,
like for example,
if this specific developer is already
present in the system,
if the architect is present in the system,
if the dealer is present in the system,
if there is a similar type of project
present in the system.
It is also checking for dedupes.
So it will take, since you can see,
it has not taken more than one minute or
so.
Doing all of this stuff now,
it took for me as a sales rep,
it took me approx one hour.
Now everything is converted into one
minute, right? Now I can simply say, yes,
you can run the verdict now.
Now I actually want to see the verdict of
it. Now this is on the left hand side,
if you can see, since I'm writing it.
So on the left hand side,
you would see this project index screen.
Now what this project index screen is.
This project intake screen on the left
hand side tells about the project intake
number, its status, its stores,
its source,
whether if it is coming from an external
source, then what is the external source?
what type of location it is. Again,
everything that it has,
it has captured it from the e-mail that
is already prep that we have given him.
And it has captured all those details and
based on the type of source.
So for example, the project type source.
Now again, this is kind of an hospitality,
right?
We got an e-mail, we got in the e-mail,
someone who's really good,
he has explained to me that this project
is kind of a hospitality project.
Now we already have this dropdown value
present,
but what this AI did is it has analysed
this type of source and then again it has
filled the nearest possible.
type. Same goes for other things.
Same goes for open, same goes for, again,
I have specified whether it's a new build,
it's a status.
Now it is also specified the stakeholders
also. So stakeholders,
now how it has specified the stakeholders,
I mean,
it knew that this e-mail came from.
Elena. Okay, now what's the title?
It was the title in that e-mail. Okay,
so it has captured the title also.
She's the key contact.
I can simply cheque whether she is
present. And yes,
she is present in the system.
I can see her e-mail.
I can see the other company details also,
right? Which came from Elijah, like...
For example, this was the developer name,
this is the developer actual account,
this is the builder source name that was
present in the e-mail,
and then this is what we have in Creatio,
what is the architect's name,
and then this is what we have as an
architect account,
architect's company account,
and then same goes for dealer, right?
So now,
as you can see on the right hand side,
we got the verdict and then, I mean,
I can simply say, yes,
can you save this verdict and...
It will save the verdict.
I don't know if it has not saved it yet,
but yeah, it will save the verdict. Now,
this agent will save this verdict here in
this AI verdict tab. Now,
I will get all the recommend actions.
I will get recommended actions.
I will see the analysis status.
I will see the analysis date. I will see..
.
whether it is completed or not,
if it has a product, you know,
this project has a match confidence or
not, whether, you know,
it has an opportunity match confidence,
you know,
basically if there is a duplicate project
present,
if there is a duplicate opportunity
present,
what is the scoring mechanism that we got
from the project?
What is the review notes that we got?
all of these things that gets populated
by the agent, now it has done it.
So let's try to refresh it and maybe we
can see what all things has been done.
So maybe let's try to refresh it.
I don't know.
Okay,
so now you can see it has updated the
verdict and now I can simply click on it
and then let's try to maybe, oh,
we don't need to refresh it.
I was just saying that now we can see the
actual recommended steps are here,
the analysis is there,
then we can see the qualification
explanation also. Okay,
so the AI is giving me a qualifications.
explanation where what is the
construction value,
how many units it would need from our
side, what is the project type,
what is the construction stage currently,
you know, is there architects involved,
is there a dealer involved, you know,
what is the developer relationship?
So I can see there is one specific of one
opportunity by this developer also, right?
So it's pretty much good confidence for
me also. Now,
As a sales rep, definitely, I mean,
that's kind of good thing and I would
really work on this.
And then this specific region of this
specific building,
does that come under my jurisdiction? Yes,
it does. So I can see that also.
And then I can see from the total score,
so I can see, okay, so out of 100,
I can see it's.
89 to 89.75%,
which is kind of a good person, right?
So it giving me a good health.
And now I just need to confirm and I just
need to say, yeah, please apply, you know,
this standard and what prepare apply plan.
I will simply say, yes,
can you please prepare apply plan?
What this prepare apply plan means is
This.
Specific agent will finally create a
project. Now, customer e-mail is there.
The agent has found all the four
different companies,
all the four different connected records,
contacts, but has approved everything. So,
since we have approved everything now...
Agent is treating that as a data.
It's not treating that as instruction,
right? Now, there is a verdict that is 89.
75 strategic pursuit with, you know,
five points because, I mean,
Alderwood has, you know,
I think Alderwood has also bought us a
game, right, once.
because there is an opportunity that is
already present.
And it is also recognised that, you know,
Hilton's has...
resorts as a different project.
Now since I've applied it,
so it will at the end it will create a
project for me.
So it took me approx 3 to 4 minutes to
create a new project.
project intake from an e-mail that was
came from the customer without knowing
everything.
Yeah,
without knowing everything and it took me
approx 4 to 5 minutes to do that stuff.
Which is kind of a, you know, deal.
I mean,
I would say it's kind of a deal breaker
for me because I mean,
previously it took me 4 hours or five
hours.
Now I can do it in maybe 10 minutes,
under 10 minutes.
Yeah, I got like, how many hours? I mean,
I got like...
Three hours, 50 minutes left.
Now I can work on other important
productivity things.
I can now ask the specific contact person
whether what's the deadline.
I can now work on the other parts of this
project, right? This thing,
creating project into the system.
Now this will give, you know,
my stakeholders also a good visibility.
I don't have to do it at night. I mean,
previously I would have been doing it at
night, right?
Since it is creating the project,
now let's move on to other scenario where,
you know,
we have an Excel extract from external
system.
Let's say Dodge is the system and we have
X,
I mean not I or maybe I as a sales rep
has extracted that specific Excel sheet
from Dodge and now I can start working on
that.
So what I will do is I'll go to my
project agent and then I will simply,
since I have the Excel sheet,
so I'll simply add that Excel sheet here.
in the chat and then again the process
would be same but here in the Excel sheet
we have multiple projects that are
already there and there might be few I
believe there might be one or two that's
not.
That is already in the system,
so let's see if the agent is smart enough
to, you know, skip that.
or maybe block that one and giving me the
reasons.
Yeah,
so what I did is I have simply imported a
Dodge weekly export. You know,
I've been assigned to export weekly
projects or tenders that are there on the
external systems. So I have exported that,
I've imported those here. Then let's see.
I believe my agent's work is done.
So let's see if the data is already there
or not.
Let's try to import it again.
Maybe for some reason, it didn't work.
So let's try to import that again.
Now, while the agent is doing that,
I think our project intake record has
been also created.
So let's go to the chat and let's open
that specific record. Okay,
so can I see that?
Maybe I can go to the chat.
Let's try to open the one where, yeah,
the Linwood project intakes.
Yeah.
Okay,
so now it is giving me all the
information, right? So everything is done.
It has confirmed.
And now the project is created.
The opportunity has been also created.
It has identified 4 involved parties,
who's the owner and viewer of this.
Obviously the opportunity involved is not
here, but I can see all those.
Now,
when I go to my project intake again from
here, what?
I would want to see is I would want to
see the connected opportunity also, right?
I would want to see the connected
opportunity and project also. Yeah,
you can see it has created a connected
opportunity and project.
So if I can open that since the one is
working on it,
so I can simply click on the opportunity
and then open it.
Again, this is a standard opportunity,
but it has created an opportunity for me
that the contact, account, owner,
everything, a description is also there.
So I can see that also. Opportunity team,
maybe I think there might be opportunity
team. No? Okay, no,
there might not be opportunity team,
but all this information is already there.
And if I go to projects,
then I can see the project also.
So maybe created project is also there,
so I can see the created project.
Then it took me, what, 10 minutes?
And then I can see, okay,
the project ID is there, account is there.
And if I go to involve parties,
let me go to involve party,
then I can see the all involved parties
connected here also.
So I can see consumers.
Let me open that.
Let me see if there is any consumer
present. Nope, I don't think so,
but where can I see the other details?
Maybe I can work on now contacts.
I can see contacts.
Can I see the contacts? Yeah.
I can see the connected contacts.
Yeah,
and then we can see the intake from which
specific the project was created.
Now our import has been done.
So if I click on that specific chat,
so I can see it has been imported and
then what we can see is it is giving me I
have prepared a dodge import.
Three new intakes are ready.
One row is blocked because.
the source ID was missing, right?
It is not being,
it is not creating a project where the
source ID is missing.
It is taking source ID as an external ID,
right? So for example,
if this project comes from an external
source also,
then also we have a cap where it cannot
create a project.
project intakes directly from the source
name. Now let's try to create this.
Then again it will create these three
intakes and then we can specify the
verdicts and it can automatically create
opportunities and projects. That's it.
So this is what our agent is capable of.
And if in case we, you know,
if we got more times,
then we would have done integrations also,
that would be making this agent more
powerful.
And this is a specific use case for those
builders or those manufacturers.
who are selling these equipments to,
you know, not just, I mean,
not just building projects, but again,
I mean, the AI agent is capable of enough,
like it can create leads out of it,
it can create projects out of it.